socibuzz.com 2014-02-09

# SociBuzz.com – Social Media Marketing (Twitter – Facebook – Tumblr & More)

Protecting your private information is our priority. This Statement of Privacy applies to the http://www.SociBuzz.com and SociBuzz, Inc. and governs data collection and usage. For the purposes of this Privacy Policy, unless otherwise noted, all references to "SociBuzz" includes SociBuzz, Inc. and the website www.SociBuzz.com. By using the SociBuzz website, you consent to the data practices described in this statement.

## Collection of your Personal Information

SociBuzz may collect personally identifiable information, such as your name. If you purchase SociBuzz's products and services, we collect billing and credit card information. This information is used to complete the purchase transaction. SociBuzz may also collect anonymous demographic information, which is not unique to you, such as your age, gender, household income, political affiliation, race and religion. We may gather additional personal or non-personal information in the future.

Information about your computer hardware and software may be automatically collected by SociBuzz. This information can include: your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times and referring website addresses. This information is used for the operation of the service, to maintain quality of the service, and to provide general statistics regarding use of the SociBuzz website.

SociBuzz encourages you to review the privacy statements of websites you choose to link to from SociBuzz so that you can understand how those websites collect, use and share your information. SociBuzz is not responsible for the privacy statements or other content on websites outside of the SociBuzz website. 

## Use of your Personal Information 

SociBuzz collects and uses your personal information to operate its website(s) and deliver the services you have requested.   
SociBuzz may also use your personally identifiable information to inform you of other products or services available from SociBuzz and its affiliates. SociBuzz may also contact you via surveys to conduct research about your opinion of current services or of potential new services that may be offered. 

  SociBuzz does not sell, rent or lease its customer lists to third parties. 

  SociBuzz may, from time to time, contact you on behalf of external business partners about a particular offering that may be of interest to you. In those cases, your unique personally identifiable information (e-mail, name, address, telephone number) is not transferred to the third party. SociBuzz may share data with trusted partners to help perform statistical analysis, send you email or postal mail, provide customer support, or arrange for deliveries. All such third parties are prohibited from using your personal information except to provide these services to SociBuzz, and they are required to maintain the confidentiality of your information. 

SociBuzz may keep track of the websites and pages our users visit within SociBuzz, in order to determine what SociBuzz services are the most popular. This data is used to deliver customized content and advertising within SociBuzz to customers whose behavior indicates that they are interested in a particular subject area. 

  SociBuzz will disclose your personal information, without notice, only if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on SociBuzz or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of SociBuzz; and, (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of SociBuzz, or the public. 

## Use of Cookies

The SociBuzz website may use "cookies" to help you personalize your online experience. A cookie is a text file that is placed on your hard disk by a web page server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you. 

  One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide a convenience feature to save you time. The purpose of a cookie is to tell the Web server that you have returned to a specific page. For example, if you personalize SociBuzz pages, or register with SociBuzz site or services, a cookie helps SociBuzz to recall your specific information on subsequent visits. This simplifies the process of recording your personal information, such as billing addresses, shipping addresses, and so on. When you return to the same SociBuzz website, the information you previously provided can be retrieved, so you can easily use the SociBuzz features that you customized. 

  You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of the SociBuzz services or websites you visit.

## Security of your Personal Information

SociBuzz secures your personal information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure.

## Children Under Thirteen

SociBuzz does not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of thirteen. If you are under the age of thirteen, you must ask your parent or guardian for permission to use this website. 

## Disconnecting your SociBuzz Account from Third Party Websites

You will be able to connect your SociBuzz account to third party accounts. BY CONNECTING YOUR SOCIBUZZ ACCOUNT TO YOUR THIRD PARTY ACCOUNT, YOU ACKNOWLEDGE AND AGREE THAT YOU ARE CONSENTING TO THE CONTINUOUS RELEASE OF INFORMATION ABOUT YOU TO OTHERS (IN ACCORDANCE WITH YOUR PRIVACY SETTINGS ON THOSE THIRD PARTY SITES). IF YOU DO NOT WANT INFORMATION ABOUT YOU, INCLUDING PERSONALLY IDENTIFYING INFORMATION, TO BE SHARED INTHIS MANNER, DO NOT USE THE THIS FEATURE. You may disconnect your account from a third party account at any time. Users may disconnect their Twitter account by visiting their "My Account" page and choosing to manage social media profiles.. 

## Changes to this Statement

SociBuzz will occasionally update this Statement of Privacy to reflect company and customer feedback. SociBuzz encourages you to periodically review this Statement to be informed of how SociBuzz is protecting your information. 

## Contact Information

SociBuzz welcomes your questions or comments regarding this Statement of Privacy. If you believe that SociBuzz has not adhered to this Statement, please contact SociBuzz at:

SociBuzz, Inc.  
Email: [support@socibuzz.com](mailto:support@socibuzz.com)  
Phone: 925-480-7624  

Effective as of July 4, 2013
